Guide to the Hisham Khatib Collection of photographic prints AD.MC.030
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Postcards, 731 (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
  - A hand-colored postcard of camels passing the Suez Canal in Kantara (El Qantara)., Circa 1899-1908; ref555; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Animals; Camels; Men; Regional/National Dress; Canals; Buildings; Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation
  - A postcard of a ship in the quay of Port Said. (Port Said - Le Quai)., Circa 1899-1908; ref556; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Port Said, Egypt; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Docks/Piers/Jetties; French Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of Port Said Lighthouse (Port Said - Le Phare)., Circa 1899-1908; ref557; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Men; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Port Said, Egypt; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Lighthouses; Buildings; Architecture; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps at Port Said (Port Said - Ferdinand de Lesseps)., Circa 1899-1908; ref558; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; Boats/Ships; Seas; Transportation; Mediterranean Sea; Lesseps, Ferdinand de (Marie, Comte), 1805-1894
  - A postcard of a boat in the quay at Port Said (Port Said - Le Quai)., Circa 1899-1908; ref559; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; French Writing; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Hotels; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Port Said, Egypt; Landscapes
  - A postcard of a statue-fountain of Queen Victoria at Port Said., Circa 1899-1908; ref560; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Fountains; Monuments/Memorials; Royalty; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Drinks/Beverages; French Writing; English Writing; Group Portraits; Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, 1819-1901
  - A postcard of a shop-lined street in Port Said (Port Said - Rue de Commerce)., Circa 1899-1908; ref561; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Women; French Writing; English Writing; Shops; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps
  - A postcard of a ship in the Suez Canal (Le Canal de Suez)., Circa 1899-1908; ref562; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Seas; Landscapes; French Writing; Egypt; English Writing
  - A postcard of ships at Port Said (Port Said - Le Port), Circa 1899-1908; ref563; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; Port Said, Egypt; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of the quay at Port Said, with the lighthouse in the background. (Port Said - Le Quai)., Circa 1899-1908; ref564; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Port Said, Egypt; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings; Lighthouses; Landscapes
  - A postcard of the quay and the Suez Canal company office at Port Said. (Le Quai et le Bureau de la Compagnie)., Circa 1899-1908; ref565; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Buildings; Port Said, Egypt; Architecture; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; French Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of the Suez Canal at Port Said (Port Said - Le Canal)., Circa 1899-1908; ref566; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Port Said, Egypt; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; French Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of four women, one holding a tambourine (Port Said - Musique Arabe)., Circa 1899-1908; ref567; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Women; Regional/National Dress; Port Said, Egypt; Musical Instruments; Musicians; Head Covers/Veils; Tambourines; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of the Ismaïlia Canal (Port Said - Ismaliah le Canal)., Circa 1899-1908; ref568; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Canals; French Writing; English Writing; Water; Landscapes
  - A postcard of fuel vendors in Port Said (Port Said - Vendeur de Combustible)., Circa 1899-1908; ref569; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Street Vendors; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; French Writing; English Writing; Facial Hair
  - A postcard of a woman with child in Port Said (Port Said - femme avec enfant)., Circa 1899-1908; ref570; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Women; Children; Regional/National Dress; Port Said, Egypt; Head Covers/Veils; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of women and children in a village near Port Said (Port Said - Village Arabe)., Circa 1899-1908; ref571; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Port Said, Egypt; Postcards; Women; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; French Writing; English Writing; Palm Trees; Buildings; Irrigation; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Water
  - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps at Port Said (Port Said - Ferdinand de Lesseps)., Circa 1899-1908; ref572; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Lighthouses; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Men; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; French Writing; English Writing
  - A postcard of a ship in the Suez Canal at Port Said (Port Said - Le Canal de Suez)., Circa 1899-1908; ref573; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Canals; Port Said, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; French Writing; English Writing; Buildings
  - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps at Port Said (Port Said - Ferdinand de Lesseps)., Circa 1899-1908; ref574; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; Lighthouses; Men; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; French Writing; English Writing; Port Said, Egypt; Lesseps, Ferdinand de (Marie, Comte), 1805-1894
  - A postcard of boats on the Nile in Cairo., Circa 1899-1908; ref575; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Cairo, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Mediterranean Sea; English Writing
  - A hand-colored postcard of an illustration of a general view of Cairo (Series 635/8)., Circa 1899-1908; ref576; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Cairo, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Pyramids; Religious Sites; Mosques; English Writing; French Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Giza, Egypt
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Giza Pyramids., Circa 1899-1908; ref577; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Pyramids; Architecture; Palm Trees; Nile River; Buildings; Animals; Men; Camels; English Writing; Giza, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of a man walking with camels in front of the Funerary Complex of Emir Qurqumas (Tombs of the Khalifs)., Circa 1900-1950; ref578; Castro Brothers Editors - Cairo; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Funerary complexes of Emir Qurqumas and Sultan al-Ashraf Inal; Animals; Camels; Buildings; Architecture; Mosques; Religious Sites; Men; Regional/National Dress; Cairo, Egypt; English Writing; Tombs/Mausoleums
  - A postcard of a man praying and a camel in a desert outside Cairo., Circa 1900-1950; ref579; Castro Brothers Editors - Cairo; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Men; Praying; Animals; Camels; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Deserts; Cairo, Egypt; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of a man riding a camel departing from the Sahara., Circa 1900-1950; ref580; Castro Brothers Editors - Cairo; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Men; Animals; Camels; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Cairo, Egypt; Deserts; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A postcard of a man on a camel in front of the The Pyramids in Cairo (no. 165), Circa 1900-1950; ref581; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Animals; Camels; Men; Regional/National Dress; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; Nile River; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A hand-colored postcard of an illustration of The Great Sphinx at Giza., Circa 1900-1950; ref582; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Giza, Egypt; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Pyramids; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; Buildings; Men; Animals; Regional/National Dress; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
  - A postcard of men on camels in front of The Sphinx in Cairo., Circa 1900-1950; ref583; Vitta & C. ie, Le Caire - Port Said & Alexandrie; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Monuments/Memorials; Architecture; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Animals; Camels; Regional/National Dress; English Writing; French Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of boats in the Mahmoudiyah (Mahmoudieh) Canal in Alexandria., 11 August 1918; ref584; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Alexandria, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Canals; Men; English Writing
  - A postcard of a man and two camels in the Desert (no.128)., Circa 1900-1950; ref585; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Egypt; Camels; Animals; Men; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Deserts; Regional/National Dress
  - A postcard of the excavated Sphinx., Circa 1900-1950; ref586; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Architecture; Monuments/Memorials; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A postcard of an illustration of a birds eye view of the Suez Canal (no. 324)., Circa 1900-1950; ref587; The Oriental and Commercial Bureau, Port Said, Egypt; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Egypt; Maps; Mediterranean Sea; Red Sea; Seas; French Writing; German Writing; English Writing; Landscapes
  - A hand-colored postcard of a street in Suez (Serie 652)., Circa 1899-1908; ref588; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Buildings; Architecture; Suez, Egypt; Streets/Roads; English Writing
  - A hand-colored postcard of the market street in Suez (Serie 652)., Circa 1899-1908; ref589; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Men; Women; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Shops; Markets; Regional/National Dress; Suez, Egypt
  - A postcard of people sitting under an awning in a street in Port Said (Port Said - Rue Arabe, serie 205)., Circa 1900-1950; ref590; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Men; Streets/Roads; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing
  - A postcard of a street in Port Said (Port Said - Rue Arabe, serie 205)., Circa 1900-1950; ref591; The Cairo Postcard Trust, Cairo (Egypt); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Men; French Writing; English Writing; Street Lamps; Carriages/Coaches; Animals; Horses; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Transportation
  - A postcard of sugar cane vendors in Port Said (no. 109)., Circa 1922-1936; ref592; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; English Writing; Street Vendors; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Buildings; Animals; Port Said, Egypt; Postal Stamps; Postal Stamps; Donkeys; Food; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A postcard of Lesseps Avenue in Port Said (Avenue de Lesseps 412), Circa 1902-1912; ref593; Lichtenstern & Harari, Commission Agents, Cairo (Egypt) (Active circa 1901-1908); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; English Writing; French Writing; Streets/Roads; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Men
  - A hand-colored postcard of four children with baskets (Fellahine Ramassant le Fumier), Circa 1902-1912; ref594; Lichtenstern & Harari, Commission Agents, Cairo (Egypt) (Active circa 1901-1908); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Group Portraits; Children; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Seas; Buildings; French Writing; Outdoors; Girls; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
  - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C., Circa 1932; 1 Photographic Prints
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the exterior of Dr. Glanx sanatorium at the Physical and Dietetic Institute in Helwan (Sanatorium Dr. Glanx (Institut Physico Dietique - no. 182), Circa 1932; ref595; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Helwan, Egypt; Egypt; Hospitals; Buildings; Architecture; English Writing; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps from the breakwater (Port Said: From the Breakwater no. 501), Circa 1932; ref596; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Statues/Sculptures; Monuments/Memorials; Boats/Ships; Buildings; Individual Portraits; English Writing; Lesseps, Ferdinand de (Marie, Comte), 1805-1894
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the statue of Ferdinand de Lesseps at Port Said (no. 500), 2 November 1932; ref597; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; English Writing; Port Said, Egypt; Statues/Sculptures; Individual Portraits; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Monuments/Memorials; Lesseps, Ferdinand de (Marie, Comte), 1805-1894
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the exterior of The Mosque at Helouan (no. 184), Circa 1932; ref598; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Mosques; Religious Sites; English Writing
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the exterior of Sanatorium Fouad I. in Helwan (no. 181), Circa 1932; ref599; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; English Writing; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of men with two camels on sand dunes (no. 291), Circa 1932; ref600; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Deserts; Animals; Camels; Men; Regional/National Dress; English Writing; Landscapes; Egypt
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of a woman standing besides a man riding a camel (Rest in the Desert) (no. 296), Circa 1932; ref601; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Deserts; Men; English Writing; Regional/National Dress; Animals; Camels; Women; Egypt
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the Office of the Suez Canal Company at Port Said, Circa 1932; ref602; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; English Writing; Boats/Ships; Transportation
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the Canal Company's Offices at Port Said (The Canal Company's Pretty Offices) (no. 306), Circa 1932; ref603; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Port Said, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; English Writing; French Writing; Offices
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of the entrance to the Mena House Hotel (no. 276), Circa 1932; ref604; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Palm Trees; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Women; English Writing
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of men with camels in a desert (no. 189), Circa 1932; ref605; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Deserts; Animals; Camels; English Writing; Men; Egypt
    - J. J. Smith. R. A. S. C. Series - A postcard of nightfall at the Pyramids in Cairo (no. 170), Circa 1932; ref606; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
      Postcards; Cairo, Egypt; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Pyramids; Palm Trees; Nile River; Rivers
  - A postcard of a man on a camel with the Pyramids in the background., Circa 1904-1939; ref607; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Animals; Camels; Men; Regional/National Dress; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Palm Trees; Nile River; Rivers; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture
  - A postcard of a man on a camel in front of the The Pyramids in Cairo (no.165), Circa 1904-1939; ref608; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Pyramids; Giza, Egypt; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Regional/National Dress; Nile River; Rivers; Buildings; English Writing
  - A hand-colored postcardof a watercolour by R. Barratt of a man in Ibn Tuloon Mosque in Cairo, Circa 1908-1930; ref609; Medici Society Ld, London (England) (1908-present); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Mosques; Religious Sites; Mosque of Ibn Tulun; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Regional/National Dress; Cairo, Egypt; Men
  - A postcard of the general view of Port Said (no.2), Circa 1885-1920; ref610; Lévy Fils et cie, Paris-Versailles (France) (Active circa 1872–1900); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Buildings; Architecture; Lighthouses; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Boats/Ships; Transportation; English Writing; French Writing; Port Said, Egypt
  - A hand-colored postcard of the Gameh-el-Sheikh Mosque in Alexandria (Mosquée Gameh-el-Sheikh), Circa 1873-1922; ref611; Emil Pinkau & Cie, Soc. An., Leipzig (Germany) (Active 1904-1945); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Alexandria, Egypt; Mosques; Religious Sites; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; French Writing; Buildings; Architecture
  - A postcard of a mural painting on the Tomb of Ti in Sakkara (Sakkara Tomb of Ti - Mural Painting) (no. 1136), Circa 1904-1939; ref612; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Tombs/Mausoleums; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Saqqara, Egypt; English Writing; Religious Sites
  - A postcard of a man on a camel by the Suez Canal, Circa 1904-1939; ref613; Lehnert & Landrock; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; English Writing; Nile River; Rivers; Boats/Ships; Animals; Camels; Men; Egypt; French Writing; German Writing
  - A postcard of the Arabian bazaar near Fort-Napoleon in Alexandria, Circa 1890-1940; ref614; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Alexandria, Egypt; Buildings; Individual Portraits; Men; Children; Animals; English Writing; Shops; Architecture; Streets/Roads
  - A hand-colored postcard of a painting of Luxor with the mountains of Thebes (no. 136), Circa 1890-1940; ref615; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Paintings; Luxor, Egypt; Thebes, Egypt; Mountains/Hills; Buildings; Individual Portraits; French Writing; English Writing; Landscapes; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting
  - A hand-colored postcard of a Muezzin giving the call to prayer (no. 40), Circa 1902-1912; ref616; Lichtenstern & Harari, Commission Agents, Cairo (Egypt) (Active circa 1901-1908); 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; English Writing; Architecture; Mosques; Buildings; Men; Regional/National Dress; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Arabic Writing; Praying; Religious Sites; Egypt
  - A postcard of ships near an open Kasr-el-Nil Bridge in Cairo., Circa 1890-1940; ref617; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; English Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Bridges; Architecture; Men; French Writing; Nile River; Rivers
  - A postcard of The Pyramids of Giza (no. 54), 1 March 1938; ref618; Zogos & Co. - Cairo, Egypt; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only 030_ref517-ref715)
    Postcards; Pyramids; Architecture; Nile River; Rivers; Giza, Egypt; English Writing; Palm Trees; Animals; Camels; Individual Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts